voip-info.org 2007-10-13

# Privacy Policy

Arte Marketing Inc., publisher of voip-info.org, and its affiliates (hereafter referred to collectively as "Arte Marketing Inc") are committed to maintaining the privacy of personal information that you provide to us when using voip-info.org (hereafter referred to collectively as "voip-info.org"). This Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information received about you when you visit voip-info.org.

**By visiting voip-info.org, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.**

voip-info.org contains links to other websites.  voip-info.org assumes no responsibility for the privacy policies and practices for these linked sites.  We recommend that you review the privacy policy at each such Web site to determine how that site protects your privacy.

**What we collect**

When you visit voip-info.org we will automatically collect IP addresses, cookie data, and web site usage information, and other information provided by your browser.

When you register, and at other times, we will collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your name, age, address, e-mail address, credit-card number and facts about your computers, profession,  and other information. 

We may run surveys and polls, they will be voluntary and you may easily decline to participate.

Information you voluntarily  post or place into public areas of the website.

_We do not   knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen._

**How we use information we collect**

We may accumulate and use this data for  marketing and service quality analysis.

For the purposes for which you specifically provided the information including, for example, processing subscriptions to mailing lists, notifying you of new features, sending opt-in emails, etc.

To provide advertisers and other third parties with aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns.

Survey and poll responses are only disclosed to outside parties in aggregate.  If the survey includes a comment or other text response area, such comments or textual responses may be disclosed but without personal data identifying the respondent.

Data and information you voluntarily place in public areas of the website may be publically viewable or otherwise used by  voip-info.org.  See Terms of Service for more information. 

We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our  Terms of Service (e.g.,  to protect our intellectual property rights). We may also disclose or use your personal information when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to do so.

**Transfer to U.S.**  
If you are located outside of the United States, please note that the information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using  voip-info.org, you consent to this transfer.

**CHOICE**

Cookies: A "cookie" is information which a web site sends to a visiting user's browser. The browser may store  the information on the user's hard drive or memory.  voip-info.org uses cookies to better serve our users.  Users may at their option and  sole expense and responsibility block or delete our cookies from their system. However, by disabling cookies, some or all site features and functionality may no longer work properly, or at all.

"Opt-in" Emails: Users may "opt-in" to receive site notifications, newsletters or other information via email. Users may remove themselves from such services at their discretion. Any email sent to an "opt-in" list will include directions for how a user may remove him or herself from the list, or a URL where the user may find such directions.

Registering: users may opt not to register.  However, some or all of the voip-info.org website features may be unavailable or have limited function to unregistered users.

**ACCESS**

With regard to personal information, registered users may view their registration data on their personal profile page. When technically feasible, users may update their personal information directly through the voip-info.org service. When such updating service is not technically feasible, voip-info.org will make reasonable efforts to assist users in updating their personal information.

**SECURITY**

voip-info.org makes best efforts to secure site integrity, voip-info.org may employ measures including but not limited to security audits, use of encryption tools and software, and other reasonable security measures and procedures. Internal access to users' private and nonpublic personal information is restricted to site administrators and individuals on a need-to-know basis. 

**ENFORCEMENT**

In the event that voip-info.org becomes aware that site security is compromised or user nonpublic information has been disclosed to unrelated third parties as a result of external activity, including but not limited to external security attacks, voip-info.org shall take reasonable measures which it deems appropriate, including but not limited to internal investigation and reporting, and notification to and cooperation with law enforcement authorities.

**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**

If you choose to visit voip-info.org, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms of Service, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Hawaii. If you have any concern about privacy at voip-info.org, please send us a thorough description to support@voip-info.org, and we will try to resolve it.  Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Terms of Service will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use.   You should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.
